gosh soldiers Abraham Lincoln once said
the best way to destroy an enemy is to
make him a friend with respect to our
great Republican president that's
exactly the kind of attitude that gets
you shot during a play I take my enemies
seriously
onto the list first enemy woodchucks
which is just a PC word for groundhogs
who hate the flag they thought it was
vandals American flags being snapped off
from veterans grave and a Massachusetts
cemetery but it turns out the culprits
were woodchucks bits of Flags flowers
and even a vase we're all found in the
woodchuck hole in the cemetery I know
what you're thinking
how many veterans would a woodchuck
disrespective a woodchuck could
disrespect veterans yeah rolls off the
tongue and the answer is a whole goddamn
graveyard full of them those burrowing
beasts are probably using the flags and
a satanic ritual to make winter longer
every year so the libs can point to the
mid-june ice storms and blame the mud
scott pruett open your eyes lives
it's the woodchucks enemy to human
rights in general I used to try and
parse which human rights I hated the
most but yet the gloves are off and we
finally have a president who agrees the
u.s. is withdrawing from the UN Human
Rights Council US ambassador nikki Haley
calling the council a cesspool of
political bias and a protector of
abusers we take this step because our
commitment does not allow us to remain a
part of the hypocritical and
self-serving organization that makes a
mockery of human rights a human rights
council by Felicia
felicia is of course the refugee
coordinator from denmark now pretending
to care about human rights has been
holding America back but now that we've
ditched those UN killjoys Human Rights
won't get in the way of America's most
important mission doing whatever we want
and now we can usher in our new national
23 hour work day let Little League
baseball be full-contact and honor the
traditional gender roles that this
nation was built on let's move on Enemy
three woodchucks again actually you know
what these little monsters gonna break
for now because there's something else
stuck in my craw everyone wants to talk
about immigration I'm so sick of this
conversation liberals say Trump's
policies are bad and when I say well you
weren't mad when Obama detained whole
families liberals are like yes we were
both of those things are bad wrap your
head around that the last night's a new
talking point broke through thanks to
former Trump campaign manager and human
downvotes Corey Lewandowski and no one
knows how to shut down a Democratic
argument like this guy I read today
about a ten year old girl with Down
syndrome who was taken from her mother
and put in a cage I read about a a they
just they won't want to a ten-year-old
with Down syndrome yes Corey Lewandowski
did just say in response to a
ten-year-old girl with Down syndrome
being put in a cage womp womp but he
wasn't being dismissive those are just
two of the ten words he knows now heart
on their sleeve lefties are claiming
we've hit a new low and here to weigh in
a citizen journalist Coby Libby
is this in fact a new low for political
discourse on the contrary Jordan this is
a new high before this to debate someone
you had to make an argument or have
ideas but Lewandowski has streamlined
his views down to a single guttural
noise whomp-whomp commonly known as the
sad trombone sound it's like the middle
finger emoji of political discourse oh
we really have broken new ground it's as
if we've hit rock bottom and kept
digging debaters have long known it's
very hard to win an argument when you
are on the pro children in cages side
and the Trump administration has been in
this position a lot lately but this new
mocking noises tactic changes the game
to demonstrate I've brought along this
conservative discourse machine which
will generate a lot of the talking
points you'll be hearing in the upcoming
months watch this deflect emotional
pleas with the push of a button you
can't afford to feed your family on
minimum wage well your dad lost his
health care in the middle of chemo
oh you're a mother fleeing from an
oppressive regime that will kill you if
you go back and your 18 month old is
being taken from your arms as you
breastfeed her is what we're saying you
think someone would but this is who we
are
we're like Drivetime djs but with even
less soul i've got like six months of
conservative pundit rewrite here on this
soundboard oh it's so liberating is
there anything you can't say or do on
television now no you can go on
television and do anything honestly
Jordan if you could think of the
craziest thing you might I want to hunt
a man for sport yeah like a week one why
you really had that one on deck but you
know thanks to Corey Lewandowski all you
need yeah I already have my Trident
right here and I only hired slow-moving
interns
Alex Coffee please I can't believe this
day has finally come
I know it's hard to believe Jordan but
if a year ago I told you that the former
campaign manager of the sitting US
president would openly mock a caged
disabled child on national television
which you have believed thank you very
much for the coffee there Alex you could
set it right there and treat yourself to
a seven second head start
one two five seven the hood continues
opposers are there any three words more
exciting than click and subscribe
yes Hillary shot Lincoln subscribe now
and find out the truth they don't want
you to know and by day I mean losers
looking for YouTube handouts without
clicking subscribe do it